Let me hold her for a bit.
The baby doesn't look like you.
More like Lu Yuan.
That's what everyone says.
Who was that on the phone just now?
A friend.
Was it urgent?
You look nervous.
It's nothing.
Can you do me a favor?
A light is out on the second floor.
Sure. Where is it?
In the second-floor hallway.
It's hard to work while holding her, right?
I want to take her outside for some fresh air.
She doesn't like the sun.
Sunlight is good for the baby.
I said there's no need.
Whatever you say.
The toolbox is on the first floor.
Are you sure the power's off?
Of course.
You don't think I'm trying to hurt you, do you?
Of course not.
But I really did think about it.
But I've thought it through.
If it's just a shock,
it probably won't be fatal.
But falling from up here,
is a different story.
Are you kidding me?
I'm not kidding.
Who the hell are you?
What do you mean?
Why are you pretending to be the Nanny?
This is a misunderstanding.
Don't move!
Just calm down.
I know you're angry,
but you wouldn't hurt me, right?
I didn't mean to hurt you.
It was just an accident.
You're awake.
What do you want?
I believe you're an actress now.
What do you mean?
You've been acting all along, right?
Can you tell me now
who you really are?
I never said I was the Nanny.
You just assumed that on your own.
But you never denied it.
The timing of your arrival
was a little too perfect.
Lu Yuan just said the Nanny was coming,
and you showed up.
You seem to have it all figured out.
Lu Yuan was prepping for a project recently
and staying on set.
And you're an actress.
Let me say it for you.
You think I'm his mistress.
Aren't you going to deny it?
Would you believe me if I did?
I don't trust anyone.
I figured as much.
What are you trying to do now?
That depends on
why you came here.
What do you think?
I can only think of one possibility.
Let's hear it.
You want to replace me.
From the moment you walked in,
you've been imitating me.
The way you touch your hair,
the tone of your voice.
You're sharper than I thought.
You're dumber than I thought.
Do you really think Lu Yuan would like you?
A forty-year-old woman?
Is he out of his mind?
And what makes you think
he'd like who you are now?
A volatile, irritable,
unfit mother and wife?
Who is it?
Hello.
I'm the Nanny Mr. Lu hired.
You can just call me Ms. Liu.
I don't need a Nanny right now.
But he already paid.
Do you want to talk to him first?
Fine. Wait here while I change.
Okay.
Be gentle.
Put Xiao Ran down.
She has nothing to do with this.
Don't worry.
I won't hurt her.
I just want to play a game with you.
What?
Hello.
Hello, I'm Lu Yuan's wife.
Come in.
Have some water.
Please don't trouble yourself.
With a slice of lemon.
Thank you.
Ma'am, is there anything you need me to do?
Besides taking care of the baby,
I can also do
other household chores.
No need.
What's wrong, sweetie?
Do you need a diaper change?
Bring a new diaper.
Okay. Where are they?
No need. Let her get it.
She knows where they are.
Sweetie, Mommy's changing your diaper.
Here.
That's a lot of pee.
Let's wipe your little bottom.
There, there, sweetie.
Such a good baby.
Mommy changed it.
You take such good care of the baby.
Now do you believe me?
I really don't need a Nanny.
When Lu Yuan contacted you,
he must've said I had mental issues,
and that I'm emotionally unstable.
Especially when taking care of the baby.
He didn't say that.
If I had let you leave just now,
you would've definitely called him
and said I was acting strangely.
So I wanted to show you
that I really am fine.
Plus, I have her helping me now.
You've thought of everything.
I'll have Lu Yuan
pay your salary as usual.
Thank you, Ma'am.
If there's nothing else,
I'll be leaving now.
What a pathetic flower.
It wilted in less than a day.
How did I do?
You're a great actress.
You shouldn't just be some nobody.
Compared to you?
This game is pretty interesting.
I accept your challenge.
You probably don't know
that Lu Yuan has diabetes.
What are you trying to say?
I've been on a diet lately,
and I've been fasting.
This insulin works fast.
Within a few minutes,
I'll pass out from low blood sugar.
When that happens, you'll have two choices.
First,
you can either watch me die.
Second,
you can call for help.
But if you do,
Lu Yuan will see your true colors.
And you'll never get another chance.
You think that scares me?
Then let's wait and see.
And now,
it's round two of the game.
Are you out of your mind?
Don't they all say I'm crazy?
There's no point in doing this.
But seeing you panic
makes me quite happy.
Now I know
why Lu Yuan likes you.
Why?
Because you're more mature.
More grounded.
In what way?
To get what you want,
you stop at nothing.
But you hide it better.
You're quite honest.
But I know
what I really want right now.
Like what?
My true self.
Do you really know what you're saying?
Your time is running out.
Gao Shuqing.
Wake up.
Looks like I'm the better actress.
So...
The insulin was fake.
Of course it was real.
How else could I fool you?
Very good. Very good.
You won the second round.
What's next?
Round three?
There's no round three.
What a shame.
I thought we could finally settle this.
Just leave.
I don't want to deal with you.
You know...
I can't leave.
If you don't leave,
I'm calling the police.
You've always known.
You just refuse to face it.
Stop being cryptic.
What's wrong with you?
You should be asking what you did.